acodez.in 2014-11-20

# Acodez - Ads Codes Dezigns

**Call us** +91 95 44 66 88 44 **Email us** info@acodez.in **Skype us** acodez **Locate us** 1/3446 D,Sivam Complex  
Westhill PO, Kozhikode  
Kerala - 673005  
India 

**We'd love to talk with you** Brief us your requirements below, and let's connect 

  * HOME
  * WORK
  * AWARDS
  * SERVICES
  * BLOG
  * CAREERS
  * CONTACT US

This privacy policy sets out how Acodez IT Solutions (hence by referred to as "Acodez", or "we", or "us ) uses and protects any information that you give Acodez IT Solutions when you use this website.

Acodez IT Solutions is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Acodez IT Solutions may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

What we collect.

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, occupation, industry, personal interests, and other information when needed to provide a service or product or carry out a transaction you have requested. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

What we do with the information we gather.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

Acodez do not transfer or share your information except as provided below:

Acodez may also send your personal information to other companies or people if:

Acodez have users' consent to share the information;

Acodez may share User's personally identifiable information with our resellers and partners, so that such resellers and partners may use such information to market Acodez 's products and services, and to market their own products and services. Acodez may engage certain trusted third parties to perform function and provide services to us, including without limitation, hosting and management services, customer relationship services, database storage and management services, fulfilling orders, sending email, processing credit card payments or other functions necessary to our business; and Acodez may share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain confidentiality of your data.

Acodez may also reveal a user's identity or relevant information if Acodez knows or believes that User is harming or interfering with other our users, anyone else, or violating the Agreement or infringing any of the Acodez 's legal rights.

Acodez may also reveal user's personal information when required to do so by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a court order or subpoena, to cooperate with investigations by law enforcement or regulatory authorities or to participate or cooperate with a judicial proceeding, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites; to protect the property and rights of Acodez or a third party, the safety of the public or any person; to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

In the event of a merger, consolidation or reorganization involving Acodez , acquisition of Acodez by another company, or other similar transaction, your personal information will, in most instances, be transferred to the control of the third party that is part of that transaction. 

Security.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We may use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@acodez.in

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you as governed by the laws of India. A small fee may be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Acodez IT Solutions, Sivam Building, Westhill PO, Calicut, Kerala, India. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

We build custom Websites using latest technologies like HTML5 and CSS3. It makes your site clean, fast loading and search engine friendly.

Revamp your website with HTML5/CSS3, contact us now!

We are experts in a wide range of Ecommerce solutions. We offer online shopping sites with Magento, Wp-Ecommerce, Virturemart, Prestashop, Os Commerce, Woo Commerce, Open Cart, Zen Cart, X Cart, Ubercart and more.

For your new Ecommerce site,contact us now! 

CMS or a 'Content Management System' quite literally allows you to control and manage the content within your web site - without technical training. Using this uncomplicated system you can very easily add, delete images and edit text in your web site on the fly.We offer CMS solutions mainly in Wordpress, Joomla and Drupal.

Start managing your sites all by your own. contact us now!

We deliver comprehensive enterprise PHP web applications that are customized to comply with your business objectives and organizational structure. Our PHP solutions enable you to achieve various business roles in the enterprise environment including people, processes and collaboration. 

To know more on our web app development services, contact usnow!. 

We uses JQuery, a lightweight JavaScript library to develop animated,interactive and fast loading websites. In fact we're an award winning jQuery website developer.

To know more on our jQuery services, contact us now! 

We custom design, develop, test and deploy Android apps of your choice.Our team is well versed with Android SDK and API with complete knowledge of the Android platform that is adaptable to larger, VGA, 2D graphics library, 3D graphics library based on OpenGL ES 1.0 specifications, and traditional smart phone layouts.We do customized application development ranging from asset tracking to advertising, gaming to messaging and voicing, GPS to multimedia applications. 

Talk to us on your Android app requirement. contact us now!. 

We develop highly precise, interactive, and easy to use apps suitable to the needs.We provide all types of apps development including air-ticketing, widgets, social media integration, website creation etc.Our experienced iPhone app programmers are well-versed with the Apple’s iOS platform with field knowledge in Xcode, Cocoa Touch Framework, and Objective C. 

Talk to us on your iPhone app requirement. contact us now! 

Our Expert team can develop Facebook applications in different technologies ranging from Flash Action Script, Java, PHP, JQuery to Dotnet. 

Talk to us on your facebook app requirement. contact us now!. 

nopCommerce is a new open source e-commerce solution that takes both a front-end ASP.Net and a back-end MS SQL 2005 or higher version.

To know more on our nopCommerce services, contact us now! 

We offer Joomla Virtuemart, Prestashop Virtuemart, Cakephp Virtuemart, and Mambo Virtuemart services to create exclusive online shops.

To know more on our Virtuemart services, contact us now!

We offer Magento E-Commerce website development, Customizing existing Magento setup with effective add-ons and process-specific features.

To know more on our Magento services, contact us now!

Our Drupal Development services includes- Template Design, Drupal Website Integration, Module Installation etc

To know more on our Drupal services, contact us now! 

We offer WordPress Installation and Setup, Custom WordPress Theme Design, WordPress Widget Development and WordPress E-Commerce Sites

To know more on our Wordpress services, contact us now!

We have extensive experience in Joomla Website Development, Joomla Extension Development & Customization and Joomla Theme Integration

To know more on our Joomla services, contact us now! 

Our DotNetNuke Development service includes DotNetNuke module Development, DotNetNuke Web Development and CMS Development

To know more on our DotNetNuke services, contact us now! 

We offer CodeIgniter Development solutions right from its installation and integration to fully-featured custom application development

To know more on our CodeIgniter services, contact us now!

We also offer web application development in CakePHP framework which allows development of websites in a rapid and reliable manner

To know more on our Cake PHP services, contact us now! 

We offer custom PHP development specializing in My SQL PHP Programming, script installing, modification, and PHP Script repairs.

To know more on our PHP development services, contact us now!

We could install, customize and configure Zen Cart . Also we could offer services in modifying and enhancing Zen Cart.

To know more on our Zen Cart services, contact us now!

CSS3 lets you make the elements of a web page more dynamic, add life with a decorative touch.It also make the web page and its content load faster and accurate.

Revamp your website with HTML5/CSS3, contact us now!

Day by day, the number of devices, platforms,and browsers that need to work with your site grows. And the best solution to this is to have a responsive website, which provides an optimal viewing experience across a wide range of devices (from desktop computer monitors to mobile phones)So it provides easy reading and navigation with a minimum of resizing, panning, and scrolling.

It's time you make One site for every screen. contact us today!

We provide various X-Cart services, viz X-Cart based eCommerce development,X-Cart Module development,X-Cart design integration,X-Cart Template Design etc. 

To know more on our X-Cart services, contact us now!.

WooCommerce is fast becoming one of the most popular solutions to easily add robust e-Commerce functionality to your WordPress based website. 

To get your custom design Woocommerce shopping site, contact us now!. 

OsCommerce is a full-featured, PHP and MySQL based catalog and open source shopping cart application that creates a profitable online web store. Our OsCommerce Development Services include OsCommerce customization, OsCommerce template installation and OsCommerce custom module development for shipping and payment. 

To know more on our OsCommerce services, contact us now!. 

Ubercart is an open source e-commerce solution which is fully integrated with the leading open source content management system, Drupal.Our Drupal and Ubercart services ranges from site building and implementation, consulting to custom module development and sponsored Ubercart development. 

To know more on our Ubercart services, contact us now!. 

WordPress e-Commerce is a WordPress Shopping Cart Plugin that is truly an industrial strength elegant easy to use and fully featured shopping cart solution ideal for selling your products, services, and or fees online.Our services includes mainly Wp E-Commerce Custom Theme Development and Wp E-Commerce Custom Plugin Development. 

To know more on our WpEcommerce services, contact usnow!. 

PrestaShop is open source e-commerce software which is built on PHP platform and runs in cross platform.We offer various Prestashop services like PrestaShop Development,PrestaShop Customization, PrestaShop Application Maintenance, PrestaShop modules and plug-ins development,PrestaShop e-commerce solution design and deployment and Personalized custom-built PrestaShop Shopping Cart. 

To know more on our Prestashop services, contact us now! . 

Considered the most user-friendly PHP based ecommerce shopping cart, Opencart is a robust solution that allows quick and easy go-to-market strategy for small & medium business models.We offer various Opencart servcies like Opencart installation / Customization, Opencart compatible theme design, Opencart module customization,Opencart payment gateway solutions etc. 

To know more on our Open cart services, contact us now!.
